# STAN SKRIVANEK

Coolatubbrid, Rocklodge, Carrigrohane, Co.Cork Tel: 086 896 5111

Email: s.skrivanek@gmail.com

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Dynamic, flexible and adaptable with sense for detail. Experienced customer service and goal orientated individual with excellent interpersonal skills and an apt for technical learning, Works well as part of a team or on own initiative. Reliable with leadership and listening skills.

Natural ability to create productive working environments within customer-oriented organisations An enthusiastic web developer currently running a website in the Czech language publishing tutorials, news and information about music production and technology.

# **KEY SKILLS & COMPETENCIES**

- Computer Skills: HTML,CSS, Java Script, Adobe software
- 8+ years work experience on Apple Mac computers
- Ability to work well under continual time deadlines
- Developing and Maintaining good working relationships throughout the team
- Problem solving ability
- Good planning skills

#### **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

2015 – 2016 Cork Training Centre, Rossa Avenue, Bishopstown, Cork

## FRONT END DEVELOPMENT

Certificate:

CIW - Advanced HTML5 & CSS3 Specialist

**CIW - Site Development Associate** 

2015 - St John's College, Sawmill Street, Cork

# **WEB DEVELOPMENT**

City & Guilds Diploma for ICT Professionals in Systems and Principles (QQI Level 5)

2010 - Colaiste Stiofain Naofa, Tramore Rd., Cork

# **SOUND ENGINEERING AND MUSIC PRODUCTION (FETAC Level 5)**

- Sound behaviour and basic physics of sound
- Music technology and computer based composition
- Recording and mixing audio in recording studio

## 1995 - Association of Professional Ski Instructors in Czech Republic

APUL - Awarded worldwide diploma of Professional Ski instructor Level C

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## 2009 – 2012 La Boheme restaurant

#### Chef

Key Responsibilities:

- Worked as a Sous Chef within a busy kitchen environment
- Budgeted for weekly intake and performed daily stocktaking
- Ensured that all staff members were well briefed on shift expectations
- Adhered to HACCAP and all standard OH&S guidelines

# 2008 - 2009 Blackrock Castle Restaurant, Cork

# Waiter

Key Responsibilities:

- Taking reservations, monitoring table bookings and assisting customers over the phone and email
- Stock Control, managing stock and ordering produce
- Managing busy floor, ensuring customer needs were met and all staff maintained a clean and professional working environment
- Responsible for cash handling: Cashing Up at the end of the shift

2006 - 2008 Bacco Restaurant, Ballincollig, Cork.

### Waiter

Key Responsibilities as above

1995 - 2006 Ski-School SKOL MAX, Spindleruv Mlyn, Czech Republic.

# **Ski Instructor and Area Manager**

Key Responsibilities:

Over 10 years of leading one of Skol Max Ski School division in skiing Area in Czech Republic.

Key Responsibilities:

- Maintaining and organising weekly rosters
- All administrative duties including book-keeping, HR records, up keeping customer profiles etc.
- All Aspects of the sales and smooth running of the Ski School for children aged 3-14 (20-100 daily)
- Training, managing and supervising a team of Ski Instructors
- Teaching Skiing

**REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST**